Contact

the.tc21@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ tineishacdnagle (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microsoft Office

Microsoft Excel

Microsoft Word

Languages

Spanish

Certifications

Adult Gerontology Acute Care Nurse Practitioner

Advanced IV Therapy and Blood Withdrawal

Critical Care Registered Nurse (CCRN)

Trauma Nursing Core Course

Honors-Awards

Military Outstanding Volunteer Service Medal

Patriot League 25th Anniversary
Team for Women's Track and Field

Global Service Award

Navy and Marine Corps Achievement Medal

Distinguished Service Award

Tineisha C. Nagle

MSN, APRN, ACNPC-AG, CCRN | Army Reserve Critical Care RN | Veteran U.S. Marine | Athlete | Volunteer

Jacksonville, North Carolina Area

Summary

EXPERIENCED PROFESSIONAL. Military veteran with a consistent record of high achievement in a variety of analytical, administrative, and training roles.

Board certified Adult-Geriatric Acute Care Nurse Practitioner & Advanced Practice Registered Nurse, with proven communication, planning, and leadership skills.

Experienced Critical Care RN & Reserve Army Critical Care Registered Nurse, dedicated to provide dignified patient care as part of a top-notch nursing staff.

Experience

Carilion Clinic

Advanced Clinical Practitioner Fellow In Acute Care Surgery (ACNP) January 2020 - Present (7 months)

Roanoke, Virginia Area

U.S. Army Reserve Medical Corps

Critical Care Registered Nurse (66S), 7458th Medical Backfill Bn, Fort Bragg, NC

December 2019 - Present (8 months)

Fayetteville, North Carolina Area

Camp Lejeune Naval Hospital GS Civilian DNS-Intensive Care Unit Staff RN/Charge RN May 2019 - January 2020 (9 months)

Jacksonville, North Carolina Area

University of Alabama at Birmingham MSN (AG-ACNP/RNFA) Graduate Student May 2017 - August 2019 (2 years 4 months)

Prime Time Healthcare Travel ICU Registered Nurse 2018 - March 2019 (1 year)

Memorial Health Staff Registered Nurse II, Neuro Vascular ICU January 2017 - August 2018 (1 year 8 months) Savannah, Georgia Area

Healthcare

AACN (American Association of Critical-Care Nurses) NTI Boston 2018 AACN Conference Attendee May 2018 - May 2018 (1 month)

Greater Boston Area

Share the experience of AACN's NTI with your colleagues, and take home new evidence-based knowledge to make an impact at the bedside. With more than 37.5 continuing education (CE) contact hours, the outstanding and diverse learning opportunities and inspirational gatherings promise to reignite your commitment to your practice and our profession.

United States Marine Corps Forces Central Command 2 years 2 months

Logistics Officer (IMA) April 2016 - May 2018 (2 years 2 months) Tampa, Florida

IMA Program

Deputy Officer in Charge, MARCENT Coordination Element-Kuwait (MCE-K), Marine Forces Central Command May 2016 - December 2016 (8 months)

Camp Arifjan, Kuwait

Military

Wayne UNC Health Care
Intensive Care Unit Staff Registered Nurse
2018 - 2018 (less than a year)
Goldsboro, North Carolina Area

United States Marine Forces Reserve (MARFORSOUTH G-4, IMA Program)

Logistics Plans Officer, U.S. MARFORSOUTH G-4, Individual Mobilization Augmentee (IMA) Program April 2015 - April 2016 (1 year 1 month)

Miami, Florida

U.S. Marine Forces South is the U.S. Marine Corps Service Component Command for U.S. Southern Command. Commander MARFORSOUTH, commands all Marine forces assigned to Commander, SOUTHCOM; advises the Commander, SOUTHCOM on the proper employment and support of Marine forces; conducts deployment and redeployment planning and execution of assigned, attached Marine forces; and accomplishes other operational missions as assigned.

Military Logistics Officer, MOS (0402)

➤ Pay Grade: O-4/Major

>Attended Joint Logistics Course at Army Logistics University Apr 2016

Leadership Health Care Council/Nashville Health Care Council Leadership Health Care Delegate to Washington D. C. March 2016 - March 2016 (1 month)

Leadership Health Care (LHC), an initiative of the Nashville Health Care Council, will visit the nation's capital as key provisions of health reform unfold and while lawmakers address funding priorities.

"LHC's annual delegation to Washington provides the future leaders of Nashville's number one health care industry the chance to hear from some of the country's most respected policymakers and have candid exchanges about the role of Nashville in the implementation of health care reform."

Davidson County Election Comsm Poll Official February 2016 - March 2016 (2 months)

Assist with voting registration, application, and change of address.

Vanderbilt University Medical Center BSN RN II, Burn Nurse Resident Graduate, VUMC Burn Unit February 2015 - March 2016 (1 year 2 months)

Greater Nashville Area

RN II Level 2 – Competent

This group consists of nurses with more than 12 months of clinical nursing experience.

All nurses are required to attain and maintain practice at this level.

Page 3 of 9

RN I Nurse Resident: Winter 2015 Nurse Residency Program position for the Burn Care Track, (Burn cares for both the Adult and pediatric patient: Burn ICU, Burn Clinic/Operating Room, Burn Step down, Pediatrics, Trauma Unit-observational experience, Hydrotherapy)

Participates in patient care under the supervision of a licensed Registered Nurse until licensed. After passing the NCLEX licensing examination and has an active RN license in the state of TN, applies the nursing process to plan and implement the care of patients, including patient and family education and continuum of care planning. Effectively communicates pertinent patient/family information to the health care team. Collaborates in establishing patient goals and evaluates progress to ensure effective outcomes. Furthers professional growth by engaging in learning activities according to the Board of Nursing standards.

United States Marine Forces Reserve (MCIW-MCB CAMPEN-S3, IMA Program)

Assistant Operations Officer (S-3A), Individual Mobilization Augmentee, MCI-West, MCB Camp Pendleton October 2014 - April 2015 (7 months)

MCB Camp Pendleton

Marine Corps Installations West-Marine Corps Base Camp Pendleton is comprised of five Marine Corps bases and stations in Southwestern United States. We provide the installation and training infrastructure to enable Marine Corps air and ground forces to develop and sustain operational readiness. To this end, our primary mission is to support training, sustaining, and deploying the warfighter, and to provide their families with services that enrich their lives.

Military Logistics Officer, MOS (0402)

➤ Pay Grade: O-3/Captain; FY 15 O-4/Major (Select)

County of Los Angeles Department of Health BSN RN I/Relief Nurse, Trauma Transitional Care (Step-down) Unit, Harbor-UCLA Medical Center October 2014 - February 2015 (5 months)

Greater Los Angeles Area

My responsibilities include focusing on applying recognized nursing principles/ practices and developing nursing knowledge and skills while providing professional nursing care to patients in a variety of settings under close supervision, typically reporting to and frequently seeking consultation from higher level nurses. Incumbents to this position are responsible for assessing, planning, implementing, and evaluating care as part of an interdisciplinary team and may provide direction to other paraprofessional staff and unlicensed assistive personnel. The scope of practice at this level demonstrates the application of basic assessment skills and adherence to patient privacy, confidentiality, and security guidelines.

United States Marine Forces Reserve (Individual Ready Reserve) 4 years 1 month

United States Marine December 2013 - October 2014 (11 months) Greater San Diego Area

Military Logistics Officer, MOS (0402)

> Pay Grade: O-3/Captain; FY 15 O-4/Major (Select)

➤ Completed FY 2015 CSCDEP Program

United States Marine
October 2010 - December 2013 (3 years 3 months)
Greater San Diego Area

Military Logistics Officer, MOS (0402)

➤ Pay Grade: O-3/Capt

Units Served with:

- ➤ (Jan 2012 -Dec 2013) 4th Medical Battalion, 4th Marine Logistics Group; San Diego, CA
- -Battalion Logistics Officer/Logistics Section Officer-in-Charge
- -Earned top Marine Corps annual training marks
- -(May 2013) Graduated from Expeditionary Warfare Seminar Distance Education Program (EWSDEP) 8600 Program, Marine Corps University
- -Completed in FY 2014 Command and Staff Course Distance Education (CSCDEP) 8900 Program, Marine Corps University
- ➤ (Oct 2010-Dec 2011) 4th Marine Logistics Group Forward West, Marine Corps Forces Reserve; Camp Pendleton, CA
- -MLG FWD West, Unit Logistics Officer
- -Served as Combat Logistics Regiment-17, Regimental Senior Watch Officer during Operation Pacific Horizon-11, Camp Pendleton, CA
- -Served as the 4th MLG OPLOG (Operational Logistics) Night Senior Watch Officer, during Multi-Service Combined Military Exercise UFG-11 (Ulchi Freedom Guardian), Yongsan, South Korea

United Planet International Registered Nurse Volunteer July 2014 - September 2014 (3 months)

Cusco, Peru

- -Provide 320 hours of direct patient care to Spanish-speaking citizens in PoliClínico Belén, Cusco, Peru.
- -As a nurse, presented with the opportunity to work in the outpatient part of the clinic to triage the patients, administer injections, prepare injections, maintain a safe and clean office environment, collect and assess vital signs, assist with I.V. therapy, assist with child examinations/wellness checks, and assist doctors with minor procedures.

United Planet's Quest program combines volunteering abroad, language learning, and cultural activities to provide an incredibly fulfilling experience for volunteers -- and valuable support for communities in need.

This program provides volunteers an opportunity to work in a healthcare setting with under-served populations. Clinics and hospitals around Cusco provide both primary care services and emergency medicine. Depending on the need, volunteers could be placed at a rural clinic or at a state-run hospital, working in a number of different fields.

United States Postal Service City Carrier Assistant January 2014 - July 2014 (7 months) San Marcos, CA

- -Contributed to organization by filling in for Regular carrier during absences and assuming all carrier responsibilities for efficient and timely delivery/ collection of mail and accountables.
- -Followed proper protocol for handling registered/certified mail, maintained accountability of portable scanners and city mail Arrow keys, and ensured proper collection of outgoing mail.
- -Route or case all classes of mail in sequence of delivery along an established route.
- -Withdraw mail from the distribution case and prepare it in sequence for efficient delivery along a prescribed route, on foot or by vehicle, on a regular schedule.
- -Use portable electronic scanner as instructed.
- -Report to supervisor all unusual incidents or conditions relating to mail delivery.

-Efficient administrative process for Amazon Parcel Sunday Delivery Service modeled after my example.

Kaiser Permanente Student Nurse Extern January 2013 - August 2013 (8 months)

Our mission is to promote and support the medical center educational programs for leadership, staff, and student development.

Kaiser Permanente is proud to contribute to the educational programs in our community by providing placement opportunities for students; so they graduate as well-prepared healthcare professionals/workers.

California State University San Marcos Accelerated Bachelor of Science Nursing Cohort 10 Student August 2011 - August 2013 (2 years 1 month) San Marcos, CA

Student Registered Nurse assigned to following clinical sites:

-Community Health and Case

Management

Sites: Interfaith Community Services, Oceanside and Escondido, CA; Elizabeth Hospice, Escondido, CA; Second Chances Student-Run Free Nurse Clinic (Jun 2013—Aug 2013)

- -Pediatrics, Rady Children's Hospital, San Diego, CA (Jan 2013—May 2013)
- -Leadership, Hemet Valley Medical Center, Hemet, CA (Jan 2013—May 2013)
- -Maternal Newborn, Rancho Springs Medical Center, Murrieta, CA (Aug 2012 —Dec 2012)
- -Medical/Surgical II and Telemetry, Tri-City Medical Center, Oceanside, CA (Aug 2012—Dec 2012)
- -Medical/Surgical I, Hemet Valley Medical Center, Hemet, CA (Jun 2012—Aug 2012)
- -Mental Health, Tri-City Medical Center, Oceanside, CA (Jun 2012—Aug 2012)
- -Fundamental Nursing, Country Villa Murrieta Healthcare Center, Murrieta, CA (Mar 2012—May 2012)

COPE Health Solutions
Clinical Care Extender
October 2010 - July 2011 (10 months)
Newport Beach, CA

-As a Clinical Care Extender (CCE), experienced over 200+ hours of direct patient care/therapeutic communication during rotations among Oncology, Telemetry, PACU, and Outpatient Surgery units, working alongside health care professionals as member of the patient care team.

United States Marine Corps
United States Marine
May 2005 - September 2010 (5 years 5 months)
Camp Pendleton, CA; Fresno, CA

Military Logistics Officer, MOS (0402)

>> Pay Grades: O-1/2ndLt, O-2/1stLt, O-3/Capt

Units Served with:

> (Sep 2008-Sep 2010) Detachement Alpha, Marine Wing Support Squadron-473, Marine Wing Support Group-47, 4th Marine Air Wing -Inspector & Instructor Operations Officer/Logistics Officer/Acting I&I Detachment Officer-in-Charge

- ➤ (Jun 2006-Mar 2007) Motor Transportation Company, Combat Logistics Battalion-5, 1st Marine Logistics Group, I Marine Expeditionary Force, Camp Falluja, Al Anbar Province, Iraq
- -Motor Transport Platoon Commander/Convoy Commander, Operation Iraqi Freedom FY 07
- ➤ (May 2006-Sep 2008) 7th Engineer Support Battalion, 1st Marine Logistics
 Group, I Marine Expeditionary Force, Camp Pendleton, CA
 -Headquarters and Service Company Commander & Battalion Logistics
 Officer, Camp Pendleton, CA & Operation Iraqi Freedom FY 08, Camp Al
 Taqaddum, Iraq

United States Naval Academy Midshipman June 2001 - May 2005 (4 years) Annapolis, MD

Students at the naval academy are addressed as Midshipman, an official military rank and paygrade. As midshipmen are actually in the United States Navy, starting from the moment that they raise their hands and affirm the oath of office at the swearing-in ceremony, they are subject to the Uniform Code of Military Justice, of which USNA regulations are a part, as well as to all executive policies and orders formulated by the Department of the Navy. The same term comprises both males and females. Upon graduation, most naval academy midshipmen are commissioned as ensigns in the Navy or second

lieutenants in the Marine Corps and serve a minimum of five years after their commissioning.

Education

University of Alabama at Birmingham

Master of Science (M.S.), Nursing Practice · (2017 - 2019)

Marine Corps Civil Military Operations School Non-degree, Civil Affairs Planner Course · (2017 - 2017)

California State University-San Marcos
Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2011 - 2013)

United States Naval Academy
Bachelor of Science (BS), Ocean Engineering · (2001 - 2005)

Madisonville North Hopkins High School Diploma, General Studies · (1997 - 2001)